Juan Guarnizo thought it was unfair
a Juan guarnizo le ha parecido Injusto
that Piqué invited Pío to this friendly
que Piqué invite a Pío a este amistoso
to sell tickets in Mexico instead of
para vender entradas en México en vez de
calling him, but instead of
haberlo llamado a él pero en vez de
going straight for River Plate, like he doesn't
tirarle directamente a la River como no
dare, he started saying that the
se atreve se puso a decir que el partido
friendly should have been between
amistoso Tendría que haber sido entre el
River's team and his own, it would have been
equipo de rivers y el suyo hubiera sido
more logical a PIB Annihilator is a
más lógico un pib aniquilador es
friendly here it's the equivalent of the fact that in the
amistoso acá es el equivalente a que al
end at Camp there wouldn't have been a game
final en el Camp no se hubiera jugado
for Cinos because yes, if they don't complain about
por cinos porque sí si no se quejan de
this, the PRIs of the Americas are
esto los pris de Américas son unos fríos
totally cold, eh And the truth is, the hunger is very noticeable,
totales eh Y la verdad se nota mucho el
eh stop crying Piqué when he
hambre eh deja de llorar Piqué cuando ha
saw this, well, he proposed the
visto esto pues le ha propuesto lo
following, I had no idea Juan You want
siguiente no tenía ni idea Juan Quieres
an Annihilators West Santos to
un aniquiladores West Santos para
compensate that he's not going to accept it, no way,
compensar que no lo va a aceptar ni de
obviously not, and the one below
coña evidentemente no y el de abajo Ya
You're already dying, no Annihilators against Saan,
te mueres no aniquiladores contra saan
whoever wins keeps Ari, give this to
quien gane se queda con Ari darle esto a
your friend, yes, yes, yes, I would give it to him, in
tu amigo sí sí sí sí se lo daría de
fact, I've wanted to give it to him for a while, eh,
hecho se lo quiero dar hace rato eh
I have one saved there, your girlfriend
tengo guardado uno ahí tu novia